Enjoy Movies, Series and Live Sports
WWW.SIGNMEUP.APP
Hey, get up!
Wake up!
Faisal!
Get up.
Let’s go.
Where is your bag?
I am not going.
But you said you will come along.
I will.
But later.
I won’t go without you.
-Listen to me, Faisal!
-No, no.
I am not going without you.
What about Meer Bhai?
You don’t have to worry about Meer Bhai.
Trust me.
Do you know what will happen to you
if you stay here?
What about the horses?
It’s not safe
to stay here any longer
Let’s go.
My legs hurt,
slow down
Don’t talk.
What happened?
The sounds we heard so far fell silent.
Frogs and insects-
They’ve gone silent
Run away, Faisal.
Run!
Uncle Meer! Uncle Meer!
Nargis?
She caught hold of uncles
and took them away.
-Where did she take them?
-To the old bungalow.
Go home immediately.
No, uncle.
I will go with you.
Calm down, Javed!
Javed! Calm down!
Javed, control yourself.
Uncle Meer!
Greetings, sir.
Tell me.
The neighbours had complained
of some stench to the municipality.
As it stopped stinking,
no one followed it up.
But last night, there seemed to have been
unbearable stench.
Howling and screaming is common
from that house.
Others didn’t interfere as they thought
it was a family issue.
They said they saw the man beat his wife
with a slipper two weeks ago.
But she took the beating in silence.
The kind of people
that exist in the world!
It breaks my heart
to hear such things.
What I feel is…
Look! Shut up and say it in two words.
I will listen to your heart
and your stupid thoughts later.
A decomposed female corpse is found
tied to a tree, sir.
It is swollen beyond recognition.
I think they starved her for two-three days
and stabbed her repeatedly.
But what I feel is those blood stains…
-Stop it!
-Sorry, sir.
Sir, you better mask your face.
Not necessary.
My stomach’s empty.
Sir!
Sir! What happened, sir?
Give me the cloth.
Get me one more.
I feel I might die
I know this is your house as well.
But you have gone too far.
Forgive me.
I have no other way.
I cannot spare you today.
Forgive me.
I am sorry.
No, Gopi.
No, please.
Hey, it’s dead.
Don’t you want to see?
Not at all!
Apparently, Leonardo da vinci…
waited outside of hospitals for hours to cut
open corpse and see what’s inside
Great job he did.
But I know how scared
you were to kill a tiny rat.
A living rat might scare me.
What can a dead rat do, Nazia?
-Take a look.
-No, Gopi!
Please, throw it out.
My mother would’ve killed me
if the milk spilled over.
-What happened?
-There is one more over there.
How many more?
You’re gobbling up the peanuts well,
but what about the money you owe.
I mean, unless you pay at least half,
boss told me not to give you groceries.
I will pay the whole thing in three days.
Do you have money for these?
Show me?
Fine. These are sufficient
Why do they show such bad news
first thing in the morning?
Don’t we have enough headaches?
Why do you watch stuff like that?
There are educational channels, right?
You don’t go to school anyway.
Why don’t you learn something from them?
You owe three thousand rupees in total.
I will give you in three days.
-What do you want, madam?
-Give me these items.
Madam, Neelam!
Mr Yashpal!
How are you?
How is your health?
I’m unable to catch you at your flat
how many ever times I come
Including this month,
you owe me three months’ rent.
There was a delay in the money
I was expecting.
That’s why I couldn’t pay you.
As soon as I get it,
I will first pay you.
Don’t the railways pay salaries?
-It’s school…
-Yes, yes.
Doesn’t the school pay you salary?
I don’t intend to trouble you.
When my wife was sick,
you helped us a lot.
But I need money too.
Please do it at the earliest.
Okay. See you.
We better close the gaps with cement.
I think that’s how the rats enter.
Yes. I just spoke to Mr Yashpal.
By the way
what happened to your promotion?
Promising.
But can’t say right now.
Hard work can get you anything, Gopi.
My dad used to say…
Our future depends on what we do today.
Mom, your dad didn’t say that.
It’s Gandhi who said that
Shut up.
Hey, what’s up, Rat killer?
-Hi, Nazia!
-Hi!
Aunty, rent!
I will give you in three days.
-No, my dad said..
-I already spoke to your dad.
Oh is it, okay.
Hey, I forgot to tell you.
From today I work night shifts.
-Okay, I will make a move.
-Okay.
-Bye, Gopi.
-Bye, Nazia.
-Bye, Yuvaraj.
-Bye.
-Bye, Nazia.
Mom!
-I don’t want to go to college today.
-Why?
Did we hear three whistles?
Mom, I have a stomach ache.
Oh?
What happened?
I am not lying.
My daughter is so hard working.
She will go to college
in spite of a stomach ache.
-Mom!
-Enough of your acting. Get ready.
This is the third time this month.
Mom, please.
Mom!
Aunty!
Gopi! Come home in the evening.
-I am making fish fry.
-Okay.
I didn’t tell you
because Yuvaraj was there.
He will think we eat fish fry
though we don’t pay rent in time.
Okay? Bye.
-Where are you off to?
-Oh my!
-You seem to be in a great hurry?
-Yes.
Uh… no.
-Are you giving it wholeheartedly?
-Yes.
-Hundred rupees.
-Hundred?
Yes. I am going to Ajmer sharif.
I will pray for you.
-Are you giving it wholeheartedly?
-Yes.
God bless you.
Fortune will knock at your door soon.
Is Mini not here?
-Hi!
No problem. Okay.
Gopi! Gopi!
Listen!
If you get a chance to invite
five famous actors to dinner,
…whether they are dead or alive.
Where is Mini?
Is she on leave today?
Forget her.
Tell me this.
If you get a chance to invite
five famous actors to dinner,
Sudhakar, I am not at all interested
in these games.
What is your problem?
What will you do when you see her?
You call me timid, don’t you?
Wait! I will definitely ask her out today.
How many dates do you need?
We went to some ten movies
and twenty dinners together.
You don’t call it a date
if the entire office goes together.
I will ask her if she will come
on a date with me alone or not.
-I see.
-Do you know what Gandhi said?
There is no success unless you try.
-Ask her out then.
-I will!
-I will definitely ask.
-She is right behind you.
My foot!
Hi!
It’s Okra curry today.
Okay.
How well you spoke, Gopi?
Don’t you get nervous
when you do that?
I should have spoken better.
You are not able to convey birthday wishes.
How can you call her on date?
-What made me say that?
-Tell me now.
If you get a chance to invite
five famous actors to dinner,
…whether they are dead or alive.
Whom would you invite? And why?
-I’ll invite no one.
-Why?
I don’t think any of my favourite actors
would dine with me.
Despite knowing that I don’t want
to invite them, get rejected and feel hurt.
How ridiculous.
Do you know whom I would invite?
Aishwarya Rai, Katrina Kaif,
Tamannaah Bhatia,
and Ileana D’Cruz…
because I think they are super hot, man.
And also Divya Bharti.
What?
Do you call Divya Bharati?
Of course. I am big fan of her.
I want to know her death of cause.
What?
You want to call a dead person to your
happy party and ask her how she died?
Yes!
Dead people would like to come back
and tell us how they died and what happened.
Sudhakar!
I never met someone as wise as you!
-I know!
I have also not come across anyone
as brave as you, Gopi.
She must have thought
I was a foodaholic.
Idea!
Has she cut the cake?
She has and they all ate it too.
Go, give her the card.
There are people around her.
There are always people around her.
Go.
Go on!
Mini!
-Happy Birthday.
-Thanks.
-Hey, Mini, wish you a happy birthday.
-Thank you. Thanks.
-Happy Birthday…
-Thank you!
Where is the party?
Can you guess how many Earths
can fit into the Sun?
-Twenty?
-No.
-Hundred?
Any other guesses?
Okay.
1.3 million Earths can fit into the Sun.
Yes, Pooja?
Teacher, can I invite everyone
to my birthday party?
Absolutely unrelated topic!
But… important…
So, please go ahead.
Okay.
Tomorrow we will have a test.
Please come prepared, okay?
[all]: Okay, teacher!
Ma’am!
-Ma’am!
-Teacher!
Tell me, Neelam.
Did they give you salary?
What salary?
They paid up to Class VII staff.
My sister is helping me
and so I am able to manage.
What about you?
I don’t really know.
It would be nice if they pay soon.
Nazia’s painting competition
is getting close.
Why don’t you speak to the Principal?
Okay?
Good morning, ma’am!
Do you think she will complain
to the manager?
Why would she complain
about a greeting card?
Anyway, she likes you.
Don’t worry.
I wrote something else
besides birthday wishes.
Oh, no!
What did you write?
I wrote ’You look beautiful today.
You have a fine dressing sense.’
-And?
-That’s all.
That’s all?
Do you know what I wrote
in the greeting card to a girl?
What did you write?
Oh, my! What happened after?
It was a nightmare.
I can’t tell you now.
But…
But don’t you ever do such stupid things.
-Not for my life.
-Gopi!
I read your card quite a few times.
Because it took me an hour
to understand your handwriting
But I liked your compliment.
Thanks.
But please next time
if you want to tell me something,
type it down so I don’t get a headache.
Hi, Mini.
Hi, Gopi!
How are you?
-I got fired.
-What?
I don’t know what to do.
Why will I be here if I am fired, Gopi?
They fired three people from my team.
How are you?
Shall we go for a movie
if you’re free today evening?
-With the team?
-Yes!
Uh, no! Just the two of us.
They are going elsewhere.
Just you and I…
Go for a movie
and if possible to dinner-
Sorry.
I am sorry, Gopi.
My uncle’s family is coming home.
I can’t.
That’s okay.
Same pinch.
People are losing job
left, right and center.
But you’re being promoted I hear.
You are lucky!
-See you. I have some work.
-Okay!
-Bye.
-Let’s go.
Not confirmed yet.
Modesty is the best policy, huh?
What? You lost your job?
Your face.
What?
She refused to go to movies?
-Why are you crying?
-She refused.
Not bad.
You asked her finally.
I thought you won’t ask.
Damn. I shouldn’t do such things.
Hey, hey!
It’s okay.
Don’t be upset.
Let us do something.
Nice bracelet!
Thanks, Lakshmi.
-Where did you find it?
-Hey, Lakshmi!
Is it gold?
Must be very expensive.
Very costly.
My mom bought it for eighty rupees
at Sultan Bazar.
Since you liked it so much,
I’ll give it to you for sixty rupees.
Do you want it?
Hey, where to?
Abdul.
No Abdul, nothing.
Leave.
Hey!
Hey, you!
Gopi, can you give me your room keys?
Only for an hour.
You said the same thing last time
and made me wait for three hours.
Don’t over do it.
Anyway, can you come
and clean the room if possible?
I will get you nice mutton biryani.
Hey!
Did the security guard
say something last time?
I know how to deal with him.
If we give too little,
it doesn’t work out.
If we give too much,
he gets suspicious.
You should learn how to manage.
You will take some time for that.
Gopi!
-What are you plans for the weekend?
-Nothing.
Can we meet?
Sure.
I am not that interested in restaurants.
Can we do something else?
Shall we go for a movie?
What movies?
I don’t think there are any nice ones.
I told you my uncle’s family
is coming over, right?
They are getting me a wine bottle.
If it is okay with you,
we can order food
and watch a movie in your room.
What do you say?
Fine.
Okay, then.
Bye.
Sorry, man. We made you wait.
-Hi!
-Hi.
There is biryani and also cake.
Finish them.
I just had dinner.
My stomach’s going to burst.
You are a lucky fellow.
Fine.
Biryani will taste better tomorrow.
Okay but use the room tomorrow
if you want.
It’s not possible on weekend.
Why not?
What is this smell?
No idea.
It is putrid.
I guess it is the garbage pile
from the next lane.
The area was nice earlier.
This started recently.
Is he going to stop us?
Bro, the stench is terrible.
-Don’t you get it?
-No.
Probably, your nose has gone numb
breathing it in all morning.
It must be some drainage leak.
Are you sure?
I hope it is not something that happened
in the market street.
Why?
What happened there?
That street was also stinking the same way
but no one paid attention.
When the guards got a complaint
and searched around,
they found a girl’s body in a car.
By then it was a week
since the girl committed suicide.
What? Really?
Let me check
where this smell is coming from.
Do that first.
Mini, come on.
Did that really happen?
No way.
I just blabbered something.
What?
Did you fake it?
Then?
Instead of doing their job,
the security interferes
into the personal lives of tenants.
Not bad, Gopi.
You are not as naive as I thought.
Don’t you have television?
I used to, but…
Nice. I like that.
Did you read all these books?
-No.
-Hey, do you play the guitar?
-No
Where did you get these frames done?
There is a studio near our office.
-How much did they charge you for each?
-I don’t remember.
-Why didn’t even take a sip?
-It’s okay.
What’s ok?
You’re sitting idle as I drink alone?
Come here.
-Do you have candles?
-Yes, I do.
-Ouch!
-Careful.
The match box must be somewhere here.
Yes, found it.
Sit.
What?
Sit and I will tell you.
Can you hear?
I saw you take the freshener.
-Who is it?
-I don’t know.
Is it your owner?
No idea.
Go and check!
If you don’t mind,
can you go into that room and wait?
-What?
-Please.
Madam Neelam!
What happened?
Can you come home once?
Okay.
Give me two minutes.
I will be back in ten minutes.
What?
Are you kidding me?
What do you think the time is?
Who is she?
Why are you going
to her house at this hour?
I think she has some problem.
-They have no one to help them.
-So?
Trust me.
I will be back in five minutes.
Mini, where are you going?
I am going home.
What?
It’s okay.
How will you go home?
I said I will be back in two minutes.
I will take a cab.
It’s quite late already.
Wait for a while, Mini. Please!
No, I can’t.
-Oh!
Then, can you wait and leave
when there is no one around?
Leave the keys in the flower pot. Okay?
Madam Neelam!
Why are you crying?
What happened?
She is talking nonsense.
She is acting weird.
I am not able to understand anything.
What are you talking about?
Nazia?
Nazia, what happened?
What does he think of me?
He underestimated me.
Who are you talking about?
See!
How he is looking at me!
He underestimated my power.
-Who?
-Who else?
It’s him.
I will not spare anyone.
Gopi, are you okay?
Gopi! Are you okay?
Wait.
Here.
Gopi!
Gopi! Where are you going?
I will bring someone.
-I will bring doctor!
-No, no, no!
If others come to know
they will brand her insane.
Who will marry her later?
But will the doctor come home
at this hour?
What do we do then?
We can’t take her out in this state.
Can you do something?
What can I do?
I don’t know.
I am sorry.
I know I am troubling you.
But… what to do…
I just don’t know what to do.
-What are you doing?
-One second.
I am checking what should be done
when someone is possessed.
What?
Do you think Nazia is possessed?
No, no.
I don’t know.
Probably.
How are you looking it up?
No, no. Not possessed.
You are Muslims, right?
We better look in the Muslim section.
What do we do
when Jinn takes possession?
What?
Nothing.
Go and get something to eat.
A broom stick too.
Quickly, please.
Gopi!
There is something outside that window.
That’s a cat.
Nazia!
Nazia, have this.
I think you are hungry.
I believe you haven’t eaten
since evening?
Your mom told me.
You are hungry. That’s all.
See. There is no one.
Eat.
Take it.
Let’s wait for the reports.
Depending on them we will go for
more tests if necessary.
If nothing works out,
I will refer you to a specialist I know.
When did you come back from college?
At five in the evening.
What did you do after coming back?
I studied for some time
and then I painted.
How long did you paint?
I don’t remember.
She doesn’t remember
anything you mentioned.
Let her be for now.
There is no need
to tell her everything and trouble her.
Was she hurt in the head in the past?
No.
Is she stressed?
About studies or something else?
No.
What are you to the girl?
Her brother?
-No.
-He is like our family member.
A very close person.
Your husband?
We separated long ago.
-Do you exercise?
-No.
For a proper blood pumping,
you must exercise regularly.
Okay.
Your narration and her behaviour
don’t tally at all.
Make sure she takes the tablets on time.
She will be fine.
Try not to panic.
Have patience.
Be positive.
I don’t think
she will be cured with medication, Gopi!
She looks fine right now.
Sometimes she acts so weird…
It’s better to take her to a Peer Baba,
what do you say?
I don’t know.
I have absolutely no idea.
Are you surprised to hear this
from a science teacher?
It’s important that Nazia gets well.
Be it tablets or a Peer Baba.
Whatever works for her.
I said no one will come forward to marry her,
if they know about her, right?
Did I sound orthodox?
Not at all.
You have your own fears.
I don’t know.
I teach kids about the Sun and the stars.
Now, here I am thinking of Babas.
Do you know any Peer Baba?
No.
-Don’t you know?
-No!
We played a game yesterday.
It was great fun.
I’ll give you three names.
Tell me whom will you choose
for what and why.
Gopi! Hey, Gopi!
-Hey, Gopi!
-What is it?
This game is called KMF.
K for Kill, M for Marry
and you know F.
Your options-
Thug beharam, Baba Ram Rahim,
-Mohan Kumar…
-Who is this Mohan Kumar now?
A serial killer
who murdered more than 20 people.
He would select aged,
single women who couldn’t give dowry,
marry them, kill them and take off
with their money and gold.
Hey!
And he did all this while working
as a PET in a school for 23 years.
-Oh my!
-Tell me. What is your answer?
Hi, Mini.
-Hi.
-How are you?
Good.
-You?
-Good!
-I got to go.
-Okay, bye.
So, tell me Gopi.
Whom would you marry?
Whom would you kill?
-And whom would you…
-Stop it.
I don’t want to do anything with anyone.
Stop your boring questions.
I’m already worried about my love story-
Hey, Gopi! First of all
these are not boring questions.
It’s you who is boring.
They play these games for fun.
No one takes them seriously as you do.
Second of all,
yours is not a love story at all.
-These questions actually-
-I have a question.
Do you know any exorcising babas?
What stupid question is that?
Yes or no?
No one has answers for such questions.
Sorry. I simply asked.
Simply?
You have the exclusive right
to ask questions all the day?
Can’t I ask any for fun?
That’s a bad cover-up.
Tell me, why did you ask?
I have a friend in my apartment.
He is making a short film.
He asked me this for research.
Do they also make short films
in your rusty apartment?
Who is this friend I never heard of?
Huh?
Shut up and tell me the truth, Gopi.
Hey!
Have you gone insane?
What if she kicked you in your face.
Pouncing and-
What if she pounced on you and bit you?
Nothing like that would’ve happened.
When did you become an expert in this?
Gopi!
Can you give me
your flat keys for tonight?
I am sorry. I can’t.
How about the weekend?
No. I am sorry.
It’s not possible for a few days.
Okay.
At least I am happy for you.
He is not so lucky.
Secretary said he will throw him out
of the apartment if he sees girls around
Okay.
Hey, do you know any Peer Babas?
What?
He is under stress
and he doesn’t know what he is saying.
Carry on.
Hey, how would he know?
Is his uncle some fakir?
-You…
-Thanks.
Hey, where to?
Doing same when we are going there.
I need some information.
Will you pay me hundred rupees?
I am going to Ajmer Sharif.
I will pray for you.
You are giving whole-heartedly, right?
Do you know any Peer Baba
who can drive away spirits?
What for?
I think a girl I know is possessed.
Careful.
Think twice before you blabber something.
Get it?
-Do you know Ibrahimpatnam?
-Yes.
It is somewhere on the city outskirts, right?
When you go sixty kilometres in from there,
-you will find a forest.
-Okay!
When you enter the forest,
you will find a 300 year old banyan tree.
You must go there
only on full moon day.
-Wear a white lungi when you go.
-Okay.
-Exactly at one in the night…
Remove the lungi.
What?
Hey, I was pulling your leg.
Why are you not laughing?
You didn’t like the joke?
When you laugh at your own joke,
it’s not called a joke.
That’s nice thing you said.
Sayed Rizwaan Hussain Shah wali Hajratt.
For generations, their family
has been helping those possessed.
It’s located near Uppal.
You’ll be there in 2 hours by Uber!
Thanks.
Oye!
-What is your name?
-Gopi Krishna.
Careful, Krishna!
It’s very difficult to recover from a blow
-We want to meet Peer Baba.
-Do you have an appointment?
Fine. Please, sit there.
Are you scared, son?
Don’t be.
That’s a street dog barking.
You don’t have to be afraid yet.
The actual fright is ahead.
Please, go in.
Meet Alauddin Baba.
Go straight and turn right.
Hey!
What are you doing here?
-You shouldn’t be here.
-Sorry!
You?
Gopi!
What?
He is Gopi.
He is with me.
He is my neighbour.
Sit down.
-When it happened, were you there with her?
-Yes.
It was Gopi who first felt
she was possessed.
-What made you feel so?
-I don’t know.
In my younger days once while I was moving
the carrom board I felt something stung me
and yelled out “scorpion”
As they moved the carrom board
and checked it really was a scorpion
I never saw a scorpion in my life till then.
Still, I felt it.
-Did this happen earlier also?
-No.
But…for the past few days,
she has been talking in sleep.
Any sleep walking?
No!
Any bad smell at home?
Not at home.
But there is a garbage pile in the next lane.
Sometimes the stench is unbearable.
Tie this talisman to your daughter’s hand.
Will this work even if she
doesn’t believe in god?
Do you believe in god?
Whether we believe in god
or not makes no difference to him.
Just because we don’t believe in ghost,
it won’t let us off.
Who said that?
I saw it in an old English movie.
It’s enough if either of you believes.
I believe.
What? Is that all?
Will this talisman do?
Won’t you see the girl?
I would have…
but she is not here.
Don’t worry.
It only happened once.
It’s not too dangerous.
Otherwise I would have personally
taken you to Baba.
But it is not necessary.
Look. Such incidents
normally don’t repeat.
A nightmare might have
had that impact on her.
If it happens again,
bring her here.
If she refuses to come,
I will come and see her myself.
Everything will be fine.
-Okay?
-No idea.
-Okay.
You can go.
-Happy?
-Yes.
-So this is going to protect us?
Mom?
Why didn’t you do this earlier?
You were annoyed
when I asked you to come.
I am not talking about yesterday.
Why didn’t you and I wear
the talisman much earlier?
In fact,
had the government made this compulsory,
no one would have problems.
Shut up.
Use shut up for everything.
A fine escape.
How much did you pay the Baba?
Tell me. How much?
You shouldn’t lie in these things.
-Three hundred.
-That’s all?
300 for the consultation.
500 for the talisman.
Oh, my! 500 rupees for a thread?
Thanks to gullible people like you,
Babas are minting money.
Yes. You are the only clever person
in the world.
Great people including
science professors come there.
What do you say to that?
There is no dearth
of stupid people in the world.
-Shut up!
-Ouch!
What happened?
Nothing.
Forget about passing your exams.
My neighbours wanted a maid.
I will give them your name.
What sort of marks are these?
You get math through practice.
Not from painting and talismans.
My mom is going crazy by the day.
Why do you say that?
She always seems to be in some pain.
She has no friends to share her pain
or at least to talk to.
She met some Baba recently
and got me this talisman.
She says it will solve all our problems.
The primary duty of moms is to torture
their kids with their own worry for them.
Our primary responsibility
as kids is to escape them.
Yes.
You are right.
Hey, are you crazy?
Your mom must have done some ritual
and got it for you.
You could have kept it at least for a
couple of days for all the trouble she took.
Okay. Let’s go to the class.
Go ahead.
I will come later.
As you wish.
Shall I buy you one?
I am sorry I had to leave that day.
Office colleagues are planning for a goa trip.
-You too-
-I am not interested.
I am sorry, Mini.
Please.
-What happened that day?
-Nothing happened.
But you left because
there was some problem
Oh, that?
It was okay.
They had a short circuit at home.
Are you not going to Goa?
Are you going?
That…
I haven’t decided yet.
If you are coming,
I’ll think about it.
-Are you coming?
-No idea.
That was a balloon, Gopi.
How can that scare you?
Balloon?
But it burst like a bomb!
That’s why no one got scared except you.
Let’s go to Goa, Mini.
Will you leave me like last time?
I have already said sorry.
Okay, then.
-Bye.
-Okay.
Bye.
Nazia!
What are you doing here?
Don’t you have a class?
What happened to you?
Why are you sweating like that?
Why is your cheek bruised?
What is happening?
You are bleeding from the nose.
Nazia!
Our solar system is so mysterious...
Neelam ma’am!
Nazia?
Neelam!
Wake me up if you want something.
Where did you get this from?
Lakshmi gave me.
It looks very expensive.
She bought it from a shop near her house.
It’s sixty rupees.
Do you like it?
It’s very nice.
Go to sleep now.
Save me!
Help!
Help! Help!
Yuvaraj! What happened?
What happened? Huh?
Nazia…
Nazia?
Nazia!
Do you have allergy?
Please don’t mind me asking this.
When you fall sick,
do you treat yourself?
Or do you see a doctor?
Sorry. I didn’t mean to annoy you.
Sorry.
Do you know her?
Why would I know a beggar?
-Crazy!
-Then…
-Why was she laughing at you then?
-Hey!
She wasn’t laughing at me.
It was at you.
Probably you reminded her of someone.
She will be asleep for a few hours.
You can go eat something.
I am right here.
Mom!
Nazia!
-What’s happened to me, mom?
-Nothing, dear.
I don’t want to stay here.
-It’s fine. What’s worrying you?
-I am very scared.
-It’s nothing. Don’t be afraid.
-Mom!
What’s wrong with me, mom?
Nothing.
Don’t be scared.
I don’t want to stay here at all.
How strange!
How did she wake up so soon?
For the kind of jab she got,
she should be asleep for hours!
-Close those windows, please.
-Okay!
Don’t let him come here.
Who are you talking about?
-There is no one here.
-Don’t let him come here!
Nazia!
Nazia, Nazia!
-What’s happening, Nazia? Nazia…
-Why is he coming here?
Nazia, there is no one here, Nazia.
Mom!
Please, mom.
Please take me home.
-Mom, please!
-Okay, okay.
Please! Please mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
-Mom!
-Nazia!
Nazia, please, Nazia.
Nazia! You will be fine. Please.
-Nazia!
-Nazia…
Nazia, calm down, Nazia.
-Nazia!
Discard that useless thread.
Do you have the guts
to touch me? Dog!
Nazia… he is a nice person, Nazia.
He is here to help us.
Please, Nazia!
Stop him and I will give you
whatever you want.
Tell me, Gopi.
What do you want?
Do you want me?
Nazia, please!
-Nazia!
-Mom, please mom!
Stop him, mom. Please!
-Okay! Nazia…
-Please! Stop him, mom!
-Hey, where are you going?
-Mom! Please.
Hey!
-Please!
-Please, mom.
-Please calm down.
-Nazia…
Gopi, I know how much you want it.
-If you stop him, I am yours.
-Nazia!
-Nazia, please don’t talk like that!
-Hey!
I will drink your blood, scoundrel!
Nazia! Please, dear.
Shut up, bitch!
I will gouge your eyes out.
Nazia! Nazia!
Nazia!
-Nazia!
-Please, Nazia.
Nazia!
What is happening here?
Who the heck are you?
This is Alauddin.
He came to tie talisman to Nazia.
Try this nonsense at home.
This is a hospital.
If I see him here again
I will kick all of you out.
Get lost from here!
Are you out of your mind?
Being a Physics teacher how can you
believe in this stuff?
Have you no sense?
Get out!
Considering her situation,
the doctor has advised shock treatment.
I don’t know what to do…
I cannot stop her.
Meet Baba immediately.
Gopi! Gopi, get up!
What is it?
Let’s take Nazia from here.
-What?
-Get up. Let’s go.
Let’s take Nazia from here.
I understood that. But why?
I don’t want shock treatment
for my daughter.
Careful.
Check if there is someone there.
Doctor anyway said he’ll throw us out.
Should we do this now?
If she gets up now,
-how do we control her?
-Shh!
We cannot take care, can we?
Alauddin said he will take care.
Nothing to worry.
She would be perfectly okay.
But…
-Nazia Hasan’s mom?
-Yes.
What about you, Gajendra?
I am Gopi, sir.
Gopi.
What is your story?
My story?
You are involved in this
from the beginning.
I live in the apartment next to theirs.
I know that.
Look…
Please get me that book.
Use the chair.
There is a reason behind every incident.
I am trying to see
how all these incidents are connected.
Do you live alone in your flat?
I am alone right now.
My roommate left for US six months ago.
What about your parents?
They live in the village.
Siblings?
I have a brother. He is married.
He lives in Bombay.
Have you seen any such incident earlier?
As a kid I saw a possessed woman.
It is still vivid before me.
She wouldn’t even blink her wide eyes
and scream something.
Out of ignorance,
I joked about her and she came chasing me.
With all their might,
four strong men tried to stop her.
I was so scared I wet my pants.
I had fever for four days.
-Is my daughter possessed?
-There is a chance.
Aunty!
Aunty, save me, please!
Please, aunty!
Brother, brother,
at least you help me, please.
They will kill me, brother.
Please, brother.
Please?
Please…!
Please, brother.
Help me, brother!
Please!
Let’s go out and talk.
Do you think,
you’re great enough to cure anything?
I have to perform a ritual.
I need two blood relatives for that.
Okay?
I will come and meet her soon!
My daughter will get well, won’t she?
I heard you cured every single person
who came to you.
If I can cure all ills,
I would have treated my ear first.
Its high time for her now,
so that’s how she will behave.
High time?
-Thanks a lot, Alauddin.
-No problem, madam.
Where are you, Gopi?
I have been trying
since two hours.
The train is about to start.
Sorry, Mini. I am a bit sick.
-I cannot come.
-What?
I am a bit sick.
I cannot come.
I just don’t get it, Gopi.
First you behave
as if you are really interested.
I don’t know
what happens to you later.
I really wanted to come, Mini.
-But…
-Just shut up!
I have learnt a lesson.
Thanks.
Mini! Mini!
Don’t you understand
what I am telling you?
So much is happening here
and what are you talking about?
I will talk to you later.
Is everything okay?
Go and sleep.
You look tired.
I will get you something to eat
after some time.
Are you making calls?
-For what?
-Peer Baba said…
he needs two male blood relatives.
Will you speak to your husband?
No.
I don’t want to do that.
I will do something.
-Okay.
Okay, Baba.
Shall we go?
It’s upstairs.
Oh! So, you are here!
How are you?
I am Rizwaan.
I came to check on you.
You don’t have to be afraid at all.
Nothing will happen to you.
Okay?
By the way,
I forgot to ask.
Did they name you after
Singer Nazia Hassan?
-I am a huge fan of Nazia Hassan’s.
-So am I.
Do you know her songs?
Then you must sing me a song.
She responds so well to you!
Can I get some water?
Masooda…
That old house…
Does anyone live there?
No!
For as long as I remember,
it has been vacant.
Then… what about that path?
When we can’t stand the garbage smell
from the next lane,
we use the path as short cut.
Does Nazia also use the path?
Yes! Sometimes…
Did you talk to your husband?
I… I will see.
It’s almost done.
Okay.
I will go around and come back.
You…
will have to bring Nazia to us.
What do you know about that house?
It has been in shambles for 15 to 20 years.
They say someone was murdered there.
The land has been in dispute ever since.
What I feel is…
Gajendra,
can you get me the details
from the police station?
Also, gather some information
on the house.
Gajendra!
Only this ear is a problem for me.
This one is…
I don’t get it.
What are you doing all this for?
Who are they to you?
People are losing jobs every day.
Mini stopped talking as well.
What’s happening?
-Gopi, hi!
-Hi!
Yuvaraj said the same thing this morning.
He asked what I will get out of this.
-Can I get your room keys for his weekend?
-Exactly.
What did you expect?
-Only for two hours.
-Not possible.
Sorry. Please wait for two weeks.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Look at you,
Instead of telling me to not be selfish
They are not your family members.
Just neighbours.
A little help is fine but you don’t have
to go overboard.
I never met anyone like that.
Such nice people are very rare.
Once Nazia gets better,
I will mind my job.
Hey, hey!
Sir!
I need a few days’ leave.
My health is not good.
It’s not your health.
Your performance is not good.
Forget the promotion.
You lost it anyway.
At least try and keep your job.
Since 2001, that house has been wasted
as no one lived there.
A man killed his husband.
It wore down since then.
A man killed his husband?
Wife… he killed his wife.
My uncle told me.
Someone named Meer taj…
Mohammed Meer taj claimed…
that it was his house
and he gave to his younger brother.
Police refused him entry to the house
as his brother was the prime suspect…
and interrogated Meer taj.
He in fact went back to his village due to this.
Which village is Meer taj from?
How can I meet him?
You will have to go
to the police station for that.
My 3000?
What?
But your uncle said it’s only 1500.
True.
I tried.
I even gave you water.
Thanks, sir.
This picture was taken
when the house was in good shape.
The dead body of a lady called Masooda Be
was found tied to a tree.
As per the post mortem report,
they dragged her, tied to a tree…
and brutally stabbed and killed her.
The most terrible thing is…
12 days after the police buried her,
someone dug up her grave
and stole the corpse.
This is Masooda Be.
This is her husband Mohammad Khaja.
I think it was her I saw last night.
What?
I suspect Masooda Be is trying
to possess Nazia.
Why Nazia?
Some spirits possess the weak
and fulfill their wishes.
-What does she want from Nazia?
-No idea.
If they shift somewhere far,
will it help?
It’s too late for that.
Gopi!
One minute.
Where did you buy the bracelet
on Nazia’s hand?
I didn’t.
Her friend Lashmi gave her.
She gave it?
Did you see her give it?
Nazia told me.
She told you a lie.
It has some unknown evil energy.
When the time comes,
we will remove it.
Let it be for now.
I am going to perform the ritual
I spoke to you about.
Be ready for everything.
Aunty! My dad wants to see you.
I will come in five minutes.
He said right now.
In two minutes then.
-Please.
-Okay.
Neelam Aunty!
Coming, Yuvaraj!
Turn off the stove after a while. Okay?
Nazia!
What happened, Nazia?
You think I will ever get well?
You will be all fine in a month. Watch.
You have nothing to worry.
I don’t want to be burden to my mom.
Burden?
What are you saying?
Your mom needs nothing
in this world except you.
I don’t want to trouble you this way either.
This is no trouble at all!
Then why are you going round the house
to find out about me, man??
What?
What is this, Gopi?
-What happened?
-Gopi, you are bleeding.
What happened, Gopi?
Gopi… Gopi!
Hey, will you tell or should I?
No. I will tell.
This is your last chance.
If you don’t say it now,
I am going to call up your father
and brother and tell them.
I said I will.
How are you?
Better.
I have a slight fever.
Take this.
Hey, take it!
This is vermicelli pudding.
I know this is not the right time.
It’s good for your taste buds.
I don’t feel like eating right now.
It’s okay. Have it.
It tastes good.
I wanted to ask you something.
I have something to tell you too.
What is it?
That’s…
I…
for me…
That…
I cannot go with you.
Peer Baba also wanted someone
related by blood.
So, there’s really nothing
I can do there.
I am sorry.
I already have a lot of pending work
in the office.
Also, I am not well.
-I…
-It’s okay, Gopi.
No problem.
I will take care.
Bye.
Don’t pull a long face.
You did the right thing.
You will feel guilty till evening.
Then you’ll get used to it.
Wow! How delicious!
Madam Neelam!
You came to ask me something?
Nothing.
Bye.
Mini, isn’t that Gopi?
Why is he talking to beggars?
He is crazy.
We need not talk about him.
I asked you to vacate the house.
But in this situation-
You have a week.
I can’t be more clear.
We asked for male relatives.
She is procrastinating.
But she didn’t bring anyone till now.
Does Abdul Azeem live here?
No. Aravind Swamy does.
I am from the police department.
Sir!
Sorry, sir.
This is the house.
-What is it?
-You are Mr Abdul Azeem, right?
-Who are you?
-I am Gopi.
I am Mrs Neelam’s neighbour.
Come in!
She acts like a strong woman
but I know her very well
I also know she is very stingy.
-How much money did she send?
-What money?
I believe her daughter’s sick.
She told me she needs my help
You want money to save
your own daughter?
What sort of a father are you?
She works day and night to save her daughter
and you ask her for money?
What is your connection with her?
-What are you to her?
-I am her neighbor.
Gopi is a Hindu.
Neelam is a Muslim.
She left her husband and lives alone.
And you help her.
Isn’t it nasty to hear?
Get up.
Tell her.
I have no pity on either of them.
If she wants her husband’s help,
tell her to learn to be a woman first.
What are you staring at?
Go!
Go! Get lost you…
Have you any sense?
Just because they are your neighbours,
how can you risk your life for them?
You already told her you won’t help.
Why are you getting involved again?
Look. I am going to inform your family.
Did she come to you for help?
Did she weep before you?
She is blackmailing you emotionally.
You were fine till yesterday.
What came over you all of a sudden?
I know what a wimp you are!
How can you fight spirits and ghosts?
Look, I say this for your own good.
This is not your cup of tea.
Your stupid help will be of no use to them.
It will be insignificant.
Hey, why don’t you answer me?
Why are you taking their problem
so personal?
I don’t know!
I don’t know how else to be
when a girl is suffering in front of me
It breaks my heart to see
the mother and daughter cry every day.
I don’t know
how not to be affected.
how not to take it personally.
Hey, Sudhakar!
Do you know what Gandhi said?
Whatever you do will be insignificant.
But it is very important that you do it.
I am doing what I can.
There is a lot I should know
about Masooda Be.
We don’t know where she is.
We don’t even know
where she is buried.
Who has the necessity
to dig out her body and take it?
We must find out about the bracelet.
Where is Meer taj’s house?
Oh, you came for the funeral?
No. Whose funeral?
-Who else? Meertaj’s funeral.
-What?
A month ago,
he met with an accident in Hyderabad.
He was in the hospital all these days.
He died this morning.
Amen!
Hello…
Hello!
Hello, is anyone home?
Who are you?
My name is Gopi.
I have come to collect some information
on Mohammad Khaja and his wife Masooda Be.
What happened?
What did he do?
Hey, who are you, man?
I am Gopi.
I came from Hyderabad.
Send him away.
How did you enter the house?
Who allowed you?
Please, bear with me.
I’ve come all the way from Hyderabad.
I have come to talk about Meertaj’s brother,
and the house at Hyderabad.
Go away from here!
-A girl called Nazia is in deep trouble.
-Move!
The doctors fail to diagnose her problem.
Peer Baba says she is possessed.
-I must find out what happened to Nazia.
-We cannot help you.
What do you think of yourself?
We are grieving over death in the family.
You don’t seem to care!
-Who is in the photograph?
-Hey, get out!
-Mother and daughter are in trouble.
-We don’t care.
We are in trouble too.
Leave us alone.
Please, sir!
If you want, you can save her.
Please!
You said the girl is in deep trouble.
-That’s why I won’t waste your time.
-Thanks, madam.
What do you want?
What do you have on your mind?
I told you. Nazia…
What do you want to achieve in life?
I don’t know all that.
All that I want to know is
what happened to Masooda Be...
and why is she after Nazia.
-Are you crazy?
-Please, don’t say that.
- I couldn’t understand and…
-No, I am not saying that.
I am only asking you.
Are you a bit crazy?
A little.
That’s good.
If you suspect the truth in what I say,
it is a sheer waste of your time.
But if you can trust me,
I will tell you a few things.
Aunt Nargis!
Wait at the pond outside the village.
I will answer your questions there.
Who was that in the photograph?
Meer taj’s wife.
Why?
Nothing.
I just asked.
No one will even realise if I die here.
Oh, my god!
Who is there?
Who is it?
Don’t shout.
It’s me.
We should have met elsewhere.
Isn’t this the purpose of your visit
to this village?
Come.
I came here to find
what Masooda Be wants from Nazia.
That’s not our concern.
How can you say that?
Shouldn’t we find out what she wants?
Masooda doesn’t belong to this world now.
We have no idea of her present world.
We don’t have to find the connection
between these two worlds.
You can’t agree with what I said, right?
I can understand your interest.
But… it is of no use to us.
Come here.
Barring her second husband,
this is where Masooda Be
sacrificed many people.
What?
-What are you trying to say?
-Yes.
I have no idea how many people she killed
before coming here.
I just don’t understand.
It was her husband who killed her, right?
He killed her unjustly and ran away.
Isn’t that why her spirit
is still in the house?
No, no.
Her husband didn’t kill her.
Masooda Be is not human as you think.
-She is a devil.
-What?
Masooda Be faced no injustice.
It was to Meer taj and his family.
Uncle Meer cultivated sugarcane
and also traded horses on the side.
After I lost my parents,
it was uncle Meer who raised me.
He had three brothers.
Fardeen, Khaja, Faisal.
I have never seen siblings
with better bonding than them
His first younger brother, Fardeen,
was a good student.
He was the only one who could
study at the University level.
We thought he was going
to change our destiny.
And he did.
But not in the way we anticipated.
Kaja come inside.
Masooda came on the day
when one of our relatives died.
We don’t know where she came from…
but from the moment she stepped in,
our lives turned upside down.
Uncle Meer and I never liked her.
Our minds warned us
of some impending disaster.
She was a witch and she was exercising
witchcraft on a few villagers.
It didn’t take us too long
to discover this.
Unable to tell Fardeen what he saw
Uncle Meer struggled within.
Then he noticed Masooda trap
her brother-in-law, Khaja…
and couldn’t believe his eyes.
Meer uncle tried to reason with his brother.
But…
Khaja was already under her spell.
What do you care how I live?
After a few days, a mysterious disease…
took over the villagers.
That day, I witnessed
the most horrible visual of my life.
An elder brother
under the spell of an evil power…
was ready to sacrifice
his own younger brother
Uncle Meer! Uncle Meer!
I told Uncle Meer whatever I saw.
Meer uncle always suspected
that Masooda was evil energy.
But he could not predict that
she would destroy his family.
By the time we reached there,
it was too late.
Uncle Meer decided to avenge the death
of his brothers.
To find Masooda, Uncle Meer started
hounding people who associates with her.
But it was futile!
Above his business and family,
-revenge became Meer uncle’s priority.
-It’s been four days since you came home.
No one cares whether
we are dead or alive.
Why don’t you speak?
Speak!
Damn!
People began to think he was insane.
His wife couldn’t take it anymore
and left with her son.
It took Meer uncle years to find Masooda
and what she was up to.
'Masooda was not just killing people.
She was sacrificing them to evoke evil.'
'Unfortunatley, she has entered your life.'
‘She won’t stop until she achieves
what she wants.’
This is what Maulvi told Uncle Meer.
He gave a holy veil and a powerful dagger
to Meer uncle to use them against Masooda.
Gathering a few brave men,
Meer uncle left for Hyderabad.
Uncle Meer!
We didn’t find Khaja anywhere.
No matter how much we tried,
Masooda didn’t confess to her sins.
There was no trace of fear in her face.
Why did you do this to my brothers?
Why did you do it to my brothers?
Even after killing Masooda,
Meer uncle had no peace.
Khaja was blindly in love with Masooda
and wanted to bring her back to life.
So, he unearthed Masooda’s body
from police grounds.
Using the witchcraft learnt from Masooda,
Khaja tried to ignite life in her.
But his job done with half-knowledge,
proved fatal for him.
Khaja!
He told Meer uncle on Masooda’s atrocities.
-He revealed where Masooda’s body was.
-I made a grave mistake.
I deserve this.
Khaja!
After praying in a holy Minar,
Uncle Meer buried Masooda’s body
in woods!
I don’t understand.
Masooda was just a human being.
Yet a very strong man like Meer taj
only found it difficult to face her.
Now she is an evil power.
Meer uncle is also not alive.
It’s going to be very hard for us.
-Are you ready?
-For what?
Take this.
From the main entrance,
take ten steps and turn right.
Ten steps down from there
you will find a cave.
What, I should go into that now?
The veil used to kill Masooda was hidden
somewhere in the cave by Meer uncle.
It will come in handy for us
when we face her.
If he knew she would come back as a ghost,
Meer uncle would have done something.
Don’t take the left under any circumstances.
That was Masooda’s spot
for murders and black magic.
Take only the right turn.
What did I say?
Take only the right and not left.
Go!
Ten feet down, walk ten steps to my right
and I reach the cave.
Good memory.
Go ahead now.
-Is there anything else in there?
-You have train at 4 am.
You will miss it if you delay.
You are back!
You managed to get it!
Gopi!
Baba, Gopi is calling.
Whatever Peer Baba wanted
is all in the bag.
I got the car.
We will go there and do whatever they say.
Let us…
Has someone from your family
agreed to go with you?
Shall we start then?
Before we leave,
you must meet someone.
Aunty!
At 2am, Gopi will spread the holy veil
on Masooda’s remains.
That diminishes the energy of the spirit.
At that exact moment,
you remove the bracelet from Nazia’s wrist.
What we are about to do
is dangerous for all of us.
We have to be very cautious.
I will find the right time and go in.
You get going.
Thanks, ma’am.
Masooda was killed using this.
What will I do with this?
You will know when the time comes.
What about you?
I know she will come for me some day.
I will be safe.
You go ahead.
Why is he here?
Please, ma’am.
Wait.
Please.
But why has he come?
He came voluntarily.
Let us go now.
-Did you pay him?
-I didn’t.
It’s getting late.
We must leave.
Let’s go!
Why did you do that, Gopi?
I know you paid him money
for coming here.
I didn’t pay him.
Your face is giving away
that you’re lying.
He shouldn’t be there.
I know he wouldn’t care whatever
happens to his own daughter.
Why discuss that now?
Let’s talk later.
-Are you able to see anything?
-Yes, I am able to.
But will Peer Baba
able to execute his plan in this rain?
I hope you are not hurt.
-What about you?
-I am fine.
What happened?
It’s nothing.
I am sorry.
Okay. Let’s go.
Shall we begin?
You have three hours.
Dig up the grave…
and when you find her remains,
cover them with this veil.
Exactly at 2 o’ clock, close the grave.
It will try to stop you.
Masooda Be… will come for you.
Don’t make the mistake of talking to her.
Because it’s a spirit.
If you talk to her,
we won’t be able to save Nazia.
I know that you are very scared, Gopi.
But the courage you display today,
you may never need it in life again.
Unless you have a strong faith,
you cannot confront it.
Don’t worry, Nazia.
Nothing will happen to you.
Gopi!
What is that?
What?
I will gouge out even your other eye today.
Touch me and I will hang you upside down
and slit your throat.
Where are you going?
This… I can’t take all this.
For the stupid fifty thousand
Gopi is paying me,
I cannot do all this.
But you are her father, aren’t you?
Spare me the lecture.
Will you give me two lakhs?
Promise me and I will stay.
We dug so much
but can’t find anything.
Probably, it isn’t here.
Pass me the veil.
Madam Neelam?
What happened?
Madam Neelam!
What’s wrong?
This chain has caught hold of my leg.
Which chain?
There is nothing!
I saw it on my leg!
Gopi! Gopi, get up!
Gopi, get up!
Gopi!
What happened?
I tried to climb out.
I know. I know, Gopi. I know.
Where is the veil?
Oh, no! It should be here.
Look that side.
Alauddin!
Careful.
What was that scream?
It must be one of the patients in the ward.
Let me go check.
Aunty!
Gulfam!
Salman!
Salman, what happened?
I am fine.
Then?
Alauddin!
What happened?
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
She is a kid.
She is not Nazia.
It’s too high.
I don’t think we can reach it.
Careful!
Gopi!
Who is it?
Nazia…
Nazia!
Who is it?
Who are you?
Gopi!
Listen.
What?
I can’t hear anything.
Let’s go.
Mom!
Mom, please save me.
I am really scared.
Mom!
No Gopi, that’s not Nazia
How dare you, man!
You chose to oppose me!
Stop these stupid games and come here.
Otherwise, I will slit your throat.
Don’t turn around Gopi.
Gopi!
Take this.
Gopi! Take this and go.
I will be fine.
Go and do as Peer Baba instructed us.
My leg is stuck. That’s all.
Go ahead, Gopi.
Salman, take them and leave.
What about you?
You leave first.
I’ll come
Nazia…
Nazia?
Nazia!
Gopi…
Come, come. Let’s go.
Nazia…
Nazia!
Look here! You'll be alright.
It’s over.
Gopi!
Is everything okay?
Okay?
Gopi!
Don’t act like a kid.
All this for a small stick?
It didn’t even go deep.
I never saw someone shiver
for a couple of sutures.
Try not to panic.
Have patience.
Be positive.
Before I leave…
I owe you an apology.
Forgive me for saying this job will happen
only if there are two male relatives.
I underestimated both of you.
I never thought Gopi will come this far.
I never believed you would be
able to manage this all alone.
Both of you had a strong resolve
to save Nazia.
This is the only quality required
to face any sort of difficulty.
What a crazy man Gopi is
Hey!
Why do you say that?
Then?
Who would risk so much for strangers?
Alauddin!
Isn’t that how humans are supposed to be?
What is so complicated to understand?
If possible, help those in need.
Whether they are family or relations
is not the question.
People…
Every one of them has some problem.
for instance here…
show me one person without a problem.
Gopi realized this.
And he helped them out.
Actually, that’s what you did too.
But, Baba, I hope he won’t have to face
any danger in future?
Danger?
Why would that happen?
Because he dug up the past.
You told me once.
Once you bring back the past,
don’t expect things to be normal.
Been a while since I ate so much.
I’ll pack you some.
No, no. It’s okay.
Come on.
Who knows when you will come again
and when I can cook for you?
What are they teaching in your new Art class?
-This’s good!
-Thanks!
-How is Nazia now?
-She is fine.
Did the police not arrest
for Gulfam’s death?
Sixteen year old girl!
Who would believe she hung a strong,
six feet tall man and killed him?
Why didn't you tell anybody that
Abdul was Meertaj’s son?
Who would want to know about
someone like him?
That’s why.
-No one enquired about him?
-No.
So, according to you,
this was all done by a ghost.
Of course. Who else?
What about Masooda Be?
These bloody cats!
I don’t know what happened to Masooda Be!
Peer Baba said there is no need
to become a detective about it
I was curious but I let it go.
I somehow am unable to believe
all that you said
Believe it or not,
I told you all that I know.
You want some water?
-It’s kind of incomplete.
-I know.
What happened?
Mini!
What nonsense?
You are trying to scare me, aren’t you?
I have seen plenty of this kind.
I am not a coward like before.
I have changed a lot.
I am not so easily scared.
Hey!
Mini!
What?
There is someone in the front room
sitting on the floor with open hair
Stop it now, Mini.
Hey!
You are crying for real?
I am not joking.
Some lady is sitting on the floor
in the front room with her hair open.
Oh, my god!
I am really scared, Gopi.
-Let me go and check.
-No, no!
Close the door.
Don’t leave me alone.
Wait.
-Stay right here.
-No, Gopi! Please don’t go!
Nothing will happen, wait
Enjoy Movies, Series and Live Sports
WWW.SIGNMEUP.APP